The Maia
Music
Open up fromポイント
The time is delayed
The wind falar
Aha past the퇴
Inb spreadsheet
tagging phải
ова
See the line
Together
I'll see you next time.
Sorry about that.
Did we make you wait long?
Not at all.
I just got here.
Thank goodness.
I was super worried.
Either way, thanks for being so patient.
I've been hearing a lot of rumors involving Sadako everywhere lately.
I mean, she did make a big scene the other day.
I wonder what kind of girl she really is.
I don't know much about her.
Oh, yeah.
Didn't we see her hanging out with Kaze Haya before?
I remember that.
And we were both saying stuff like,
Oh my gosh, are the two of them dating now?
There's no way that would ever happen.
You think so?
If Kaze Haya did actually like her, would it be that weird?
Of course it would!
She'd never even stand a chance!
Kaze Haya is a total good guy, so naturally he's gonna be overly nice to her!
Besides, if you'd like anyone to beat you, Kurumi!
No, that's impossible!
What are you saying?
You two are so close, aren't you?
That's only because we both went to the same middle school.
Jeez, why don't you two just go out already?
Not happening.
Even if you don't feel that way, maybe Kaze Haya will eventually fall for you.
This only started recently.
But it seems there's been somewhat of a...
mysterious phenomenon happening in the way my classmates interact with me.
Hey, it's Sadako!
Hey, you, make a goofy face to see if she laughs.
What?
Oh, you mean like a funny one?
Look!
Oh, uh, okay.
It didn't work.
Mission failed.
I'm not sure how to describe it because it's such a new feeling.
But I'm just glad people aren't avoiding me anymore.
Oh, you don't know?
People are saying that fortune comes to those who make Sadako smile.
Fortune?
This is the first time anyone's said that about me.
I'm happy for you.
Okay, I'll smile for them.
Hey, Nakanishi, tell Sadako a joke.
Right.
Why'd the hen cross the road to get to the other side?
Funny, right?
Uh, that one was definitely a fail.
Yeah, in more ways than one.
Why does that happen every time you try to smile, Sadako?
Morning.
Hey.
Morning!
Yano, Yoshida, good morning to you both.
Look at you.
It seems like you've recently become pretty good friends with Hirano and Endo as well.
Huh?
F-friend?
Right?
All of us are friends now.
I didn't actually realize it, but...
I-I'm so happy.
This is the best moment of my life.
Speaking of, it's kind of a pain to keep using your last names.
Can we go off a first name basis?
Sure.
Just go ahead and call me Eko.
And I'm Tomo.
All right, then you two can feel free to just call us Chizu and Ayane.
Okay.
So, Chizu and Ayane.
Got it.
Thanks for making sure to include me in there.
So...
So smooth.
Huh?
What is...
That's how everyone gets comfortable calling each other by their first names.
I'm learning a lot today.
No, this is honestly not how it usually goes at all.
Normally, you'd go with the flow and start using them as you become closer with people.
I mean, you get it, don't you?
Eko.
Tomo.
Chizu.
And Ayane.
See?
We want you to use first names, too.
Huh?
Seriously?
What are you waiting for?
Give it a little try.
Ayane...
Oh!
She said it!
Ch-ch-ch-ch-chizu!
Are you gonna be okay?
E-e-e-e-e-eko...
T-t-tomo...
Wow!
That's different.
Ah, I like it.
Come on, Sawago.
Again, again!
You gotta practice!
I guess they really liked that.
You're too formal with people when you initially meet them anyway.
You should try calling girls in class by their first names from now on.
Their first names? Isn't that being too friendly?
I don't think it'll be a problem.
Guess you're seriously not used to these kind of things, huh?
Well, I'm sure it won't happen right away, so just start with your friends.
Ah, I think I may have found a good test subject.
Test subject?
As an experiment, why don't you try calling him by his first name?
What? My justice... No, I can't, Yano!
Yano, huh?
I mean, uh, Ayane? That's too difficult for me!
Come on, how do you think you're supposed to get closer to people if you don't try?
Yano-Chin's a sadist.
After all, weren't you going to do your best?
Good morning, hey!
Oh, Kasehaya! Sanako said she had something to say to you.
Hmm?
Go!
K-Kasehaya!
That's his last name.
Yeah? What?
Hi.
Hi?
Kasehaya!
It's harder with guys, so that's why I'm saying you should stick to only girls for the time being.
As pushy as always.
Th-that was nerve-wracking!
Right, start with the girls.
Okay, I'll do my best.
And for the boys, I'll keep doing things the way I have been.
I see.
So that was all Yano's idea, then.
Boys.
He's always so kind to me, just like Yano and Yoshida are.
And he talks to everyone regardless of their gender, but...
Since Kuro Numa doesn't usually call out to me like that.
Kasehaya is... a boy.
I wonder what she was wanting to say.
He's similar to Yano and Yoshida, but also very different.
How do I put this?
He's just...
A boy.
Uh, for today's homeroom, we're deciding on the field day committee member.
Choosing is a pain, so I've decided the P.E. rep wins.
There, that was easy.
That's me.
Huh?
There was no chance to volunteer.
So get to work.
And if you're wondering who's in charge of the committee, it's me.
So if you don't go, I'll spread all of your embarrassment.
All right, all right, I know.
I'll make sure I'm always there, okay?
Listen up.
Every single one of you better take first place.
We don't have enough people here,
so anyone who's athletic will compete in several events.
Anybody experienced in a sport must play that sport.
If you don't think you're athletic enough,
don't even show up!
What a scumbag.
And so that leaves us with...
Gah!
My arms want to move.
My legs are pumped to go.
It's almost go time.
My moment is coming.
Yes!
And let the fire burn in you.
We're gonna win.
First place is ours.
We're gonna take them all down.
These two are exhausting.
I have to make sure I don't drag everyone down.
Kuro Numa, do you play soccer?
Oh, no, not at all.
Is that so?
Not surprising since you don't look all that athletic.
I'm gonna give field day everything I've got.
You don't have to, you know?
I'd suggest you take the day off.
I have an idea.
Why don't we all get a little practice in during our lunch break?
Huh, good idea.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
I think that would really help.
Okay.
Let's give it our all then.
I'll do my best.
Practice for field day, huh?
I don't really wanna.
But at least having Kazehaya around will make it more interesting.
Speaking of Kazehaya,
the poor guy was volunteered instantly, wasn't he?
Yep.
By the way, isn't homeroom our next class coming up?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I wonder if we're gonna decide everyone's field day events.
Oh, that reminds me.
Kazehaya's on the field day committee.
He's representing class D.
Wow, is he really?
Maybe you should become a member of the committee also.
What?
You think I should?
There's really no reason not to, so why not try it out?
This could end up being how you and Kazehaya get together.
I don't think so.
How many times do I have to tell you that's not gonna happen?
Though I wouldn't actually mind becoming a committee member.
See?
So try.
I can't volunteer myself for the position.
It's too embarrassing.
Don't worry.
We can be the ones who recommend you.
Your face is so red, Kurumi.
All right, heads up!
Hey, Saniko!
Got it!
Oopsie-doodles.
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Hmm, I guess playing an actual match is a little too advanced.
Sadako, you'll need to start with the basics of kicking the ball.
I'm sorry I'm so incompetent.
It's fine.
We know you won't be perfect when you don't have experience.
You should really try smiling instead of looking so sad, Sadako.
The people on the opposing team might freak out if they see her smile.
Or maybe it'll give us enough good fortune to win.
Hey, Chizu!
If we don't start heading back soon, then we'll be late for fifth period.
Oh, you gotta be kidding.
Is it just me or does lunch break feel shorter?
Yikes, and the sports teams use the fields after school, so that's out.
Ugh, this is bad.
I'm already weighing everyone down during practice.
Come on, Sawako, you can't keep wasting their precious time.
I have to train on my own.
But I'll need to get a soccer ball.
I must train on my own.
What the heck are you mumbling about?
You're scaring me.
I need to get a soccer ball.
I suddenly started chanting.
Come on, time to go.
Looks like the guys are still practicing.
It's Kaze Haya.
Those dummies.
I guess they're finding time to goof off like usual.
He's having fun.
I'm happy I finally get to see him playing sports.
I wonder what he's like when he plays softball.
We seriously gotta go or we'll definitely be late for our fifth period.
Right.
We're heading back inside now.
Sure.
Okay.
Pigtails.
Come on.
We gotta go in.
Right.
Sadako.
Why are you standing there and zoning out?
It's time to head back.
Whoa, your face is red.
Wait, it is?
Did you overexert yourself while running?
No, I don't think I did.
Huh?
What?
Nothing special happened, right?
If not, why am I blushing?
He wasn't even that close.
All he did was turn around and start going back to class.
I just couldn't take my eyes off him for some reason.
So I watched him walk away.
All rise.
Bow.
It's over!
Hey, Yanochi, let's go get something to eat.
You too, Sadako.
We could get some ramen again.
No, I'll get fat if I keep eating out with you.
Aw.
Anyway, don't you have shopping to do, Chizu?
Yep, I gotta grab a red T-shirt to help me stand out for field day.
Hey, Sadako, did you want to come?
Um, I have to do a few things like water the garden, so if it's okay, I'll join next time.
That's so.
Could we tag along with you until you're finished and then go shopping?
With the three of us, it'll be faster, too.
Uh, no.
I think I've got it.
But in the future...
I may try to take you up on your offer to help out.
Hee, we'll be there when you need us.
We can always go shopping some other time.
Okay.
Knowing those two, if I mention training on my own, they'll probably help me even though they're busy.
So next time, when you don't have any plans, I'll happily accept your help.
Thank you.
Kazehaya.
What are you doing today?
Hmm?
Oh, got a committee meeting.
It's Kazehaya.
Huh?
Busy with field day stuff, huh?
Oh, all right.
He just dumped that on you.
Yeah.
Seriously, what am I even doing right now?
What?
You want me to lend you a soccer ball?
Yes, sir.
I'd really appreciate it.
Sorry.
No.
We can't just give them out so you kids can lose them.
Is there any way to convince you?
I promise to return it when I'm done.
I already said no.
I had my hopes set on that working.
I guess I'll have to buy my own ball to practice with now.
There goes my New Year's savings.
Hey, Joe, can I leave this open?
I think so.
This is where I had my first real conversation with Kazehaya.
It's true.
you're on the field day committee oh you're here too kurumi that's great guess we both have awful
luck huh sit that seat's free oh thank you and also thanks for that cd you lent me my pleasure
would it be okay if i borrow one of your cds in return yeah sure that should be fine awesome
you know the album that was released before the one i lent you
uh kaze haya are you listening my bad what were you talking about the cd that was released before
the one i lent you oh got it i'll be sure to bring it next time
now what are you up to
what hour was that bell for
hang on what hour was that bell for
uh
I have an idea.
I don't know why. I can't smile normally like other people seem to.
The atmosphere feels a little bit different than usual.
That's why, instead of a smile...
Let this reach from me to you.
I don't know why.
All that will be the answer
The stars flying the point...
Only one.
New friend.